Be More
Oh
It must be more than I need you
More than I love you
Be more than wishes on stars
High above you
If words could just hold you
Tell me you feel me
Oh, just to know you
Tell me you see me
I couldn't have said it (said it)
You must have just read it (read it)
In my eyes
Darling, please
Let it be more
Be more
It must be more than I want you
More than I touch you
Be more than dancing in raindrops
Falling to touch you, whoa, just to touch you, oh
If words could just hold you
Tell me you feel me
Oh, just to know you
Tell me you see me, yeah
I couldn't have said it (said it)
You must have just read it
In my eyes
Let it be more
Be more
Darling, be more
If words could just hold you
Tell me you feel me
Oh, just to know you
Tell me you see me
I couldn't have said it
You must have just read it
In my eyes
Darling, please
Let it be more